<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OK Commit</title>
    <link>http://www.okcommit.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on OK Commit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 12:42:09 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.okcommit.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Us</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/about/us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 12:42:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/about/us/</guid>
      <description>About Us This is a test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Is OKR Different From OKC?</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/how-is-okr-different-from-okc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 18:12:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/how-is-okr-different-from-okc/</guid>
      <description>OKR is a framework. A framework is a broad but incomplete structure which supports an approach to achieve an outcome. A framework leaves room to add and remove practices and tools.
OKC is an opinionated methodology that has a defined set of principles, tools, and practices. OKC operates within the OKR framework. The OKC methodology is not a list of suggestions or choices. Even though the elements of OKC individually have value, the real value comes from applying all aspects of the methodology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is an Objective?</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-is-an-objective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:26:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-is-an-objective/</guid>
      <description>Objectives are concise statements that describe what you want to achieve. They should inspire, engage, challenge, and motivate the team. Objectives are time-bound and qualitative.
On May 25, 1961, John F. Kennedy before the joint session of congress, set the following national goal:
 “I believe that this nation should commit itself to achieving the goal, before this decade is out, of landing a man on the moon and returning him safely to the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commit to Ensure Your Success</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/commit-to-ensure-your-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 16:03:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/commit-to-ensure-your-success/</guid>
      <description>According to a recent study done by U.S. News, 80% of New Year’s resolution makers become New Year’s resolution breakers by the second week of February. Similarly, many organizations suffer a similar fate with their OKR implementation. A common mistake many teams make with their objectives and key results is that they “set and forget” goals.
In both cases, the reason they fail is that they don’t take small steps and review progress on a regular basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commitment Meeting Best Practices</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/commitment-meeting-best-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:19:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/commitment-meeting-best-practices/</guid>
      <description>This article discusses some logistics and best practices for your commitment meetings.
Types of Meetings Depending on your commitment type, you have a few options for your meetings:
 Commitment meetings are 10-15 minutes long and cover the 4-question agenda. Most teams will use commitment meetings. Commitment meetings are best when the team makes small outcome commitments or uses projects to influence the key results. Commitment huddles are 5 minutes long and are best when using leveraged behavior commitments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Types of Commitments</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-three-types-of-commitments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-three-types-of-commitments/</guid>
      <description>Making regular commitments towards the key results is where the real execution takes place. Let’s discuss how to tailor commitment making for your team.
Types of Commitments There are three types of commitments to consider:
 Leveraged behaviors track the specific behaviors you want the team to perform throughout the week. It holds the team accountable for performing the behavior rather than producing the result. You can track leveraged behaviors on an individual or team basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes a Good Key Result?</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-makes-a-good-key-result/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 12:51:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-makes-a-good-key-result/</guid>
      <description>Your key results should be:
Measurable A key result is quantifiable and should have an X and Y. You should be able to collect data for the key result and measure progress during the cycle.
Time Bound A key result should have a date for the Y value. We recommend short and strict time frames for key results to help the team focus and reduce uncertainty. The date should align with your organization’s goal setting cycles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Your Key Results</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/discovering-your-key-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:58:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/discovering-your-key-results/</guid>
      <description>In determining your key results, ask, “What does success look like for this objective?” A common mistake when creating key results is to define activities instead of outcomes for key results. Your key results should measure a result, not effort. We define success as improving something and making an impact instead of completing a project or task. Making an impact can include sustaining a metric and increasing or decreasing a metric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes a Good Objective?</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-makes-a-good-objective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:45:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-makes-a-good-objective/</guid>
      <description>Your objectives should be:
High impact Achieving a team objective should impact your organization. The achievement should be worthy of a celebration. Avoid creating “business as usual” objectives. We define “business as usual” objectives as those written based on what the team believes they can achieve without changing their behavior. Outcomes of this process are to help the team evolve, continue to innovate, and drive efficiency.
Clear Use clear language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Your Team Objective</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/discovering-your-team-objective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:39:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/discovering-your-team-objective/</guid>
      <description>The following questions are helpful in discovering your team objective:
 How can we contribute to one of the strategic objectives?
 Which of the key results associated with a strategic objective can we impact?
 Which area of our team’s performance would we want to improve the most to achieve a strategic objective?
 What area of excellence for our team could we improve to an even higher level to ensure the organization achieves a strategic objective?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Types of Objectives</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-three-types-of-objectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:29:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-three-types-of-objectives/</guid>
      <description>There are three types of objectives:
Strategic Objectives Strategic objectives are your organization’s high-level and longer-term objectives. Organizations typically set strategic objectives annually. The organization will review these objectives throughout the year. However, organizations may set strategic objectives more frequent with the understanding that overhead exists with managing these objectives. Organizations establish strategic objectives first before they set any other objective types.
Team Objectives Team objectives are tactical objectives created by a team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Sustain OKC</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/how-to-sustain-okrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:11:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/how-to-sustain-okrs/</guid>
      <description>While OKC principles seem simple, sustaining the process is harder than you think. Organizations implementing OKC will run into three issues:
 The novelty wears off in about 8 to 10 weeks. Team members will lose interest without reinforcement. The internal or external conditions may change. New opportunities or threats emerge that may impact an objective. The team’s assumption and predictions were wrong for their objective and key results. With OKC, you are making both strategic and execution bets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Key Result?</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-is-a-key-result/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 09:47:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-is-a-key-result/</guid>
      <description>Key results measure your progress towards achievement of a given objective. If the objective is the “what”, the key result is the “how” – how you will know if you succeeded. Key results are quantitative and will use a number in the statement. The sum of the key results will result in a desired outcome for the objective and drive the right behavior. The key results must also be measurable. If you can’t collect the data, then you can’t measure your progress towards the key result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Answer Is to Focus on What Matters</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-answer-is-to-focus-on-what-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:17:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-answer-is-to-focus-on-what-matters/</guid>
      <description>Many consider Andy Grove, the former CEO of Intel, the father of OKRs. In his book, High Output Management, he first spoke about “Objectives and Key Results” regarding running a successful management by objectives (MBO) system. He stated:
 The one thing an MBO system should provide par excellence is focus. This can only happen if we keep the number of objectives small. In practice, this is rare, and here, as elsewhere, we fall victim to our inability to say “no”—in this case, to too many objectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Is Hard</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/change-is-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:10:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/change-is-hard/</guid>
      <description>Why is change so hard for your team members? In particular, if the strategic objectives are so important to the organization, why do team members struggle to execute against their goals? Some reasons could include:
 The goals are unrealistic to achieve or lack clarity. Sometimes, there are too many goals to complete for a team member. In other cases, the goal might not be influenceable. As a result, the team member does not believe they will succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Mission to Vision: Your Organization Strategy</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/from-mission-to-vision-your-organization-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 16:40:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/from-mission-to-vision-your-organization-strategy/</guid>
      <description>OKC fits within the broader strategic context of an organization.
Your organization should have both a mission and a set of values. The mission answers the question “Why do we exist?” The organizational values are traits or qualities that the organization considers worthwhile and define how you should behave. The outer box in diagram represents your mission and values. Your mission and values help the organization understand what “is in” and what “is out” of the box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Facilitation</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/services/facilitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 12:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/services/facilitation/</guid>
      <description>We can help your organization with your OKR process through a comprehensive OKR implementation tailored for your organization that includes strategy sessions, manager certification, remote coaching sessions, and launch reviews to ensure sustainable results.
The facilitation includes:
 An executive leadership 1-day strategy session to develop annual stategic objectives and key results for organziation. A manager 2-day training session to certify your managers in the OKC process and establish team objectives and key results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Coaching</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/services/remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/services/remote/</guid>
      <description>If you are not interested in a comprehensive OKR implementation, we can provide a series of remote coaching sessions for your internal coaches (shepherds) and webinars to help guide your managers in your OKR implementation.
Remote coaching is appropriate for teams with OKR process experience or other goal setting methodologies.
Interested in learning more? Fill out the form below and we will contact you with additional information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/services/officehours/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 12:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/services/officehours/</guid>
      <description>We provide one-off consultations to answer your OKR-related questions and help you diagnose adoption and process issues.
The hours can be used in various ways:
 Answer OKR process questions or specific questions about your OKR implementation. Diagnose &amp;ldquo;piping&amp;rdquo; issues with objectives and a lack of meaningful progress towards key results. Discuss adoption challenges with the OKR process. Answer specific questions about your implementation. Provide quick assessments of your OKR implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>