<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Objectives on OK Commit</title>
    <link>http://www.okcommit.com/tags/objectives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Objectives on OK Commit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:26:22 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.okcommit.com/tags/objectives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is an Objective?</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-is-an-objective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:26:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-is-an-objective/</guid>
      <description>Objectives are concise statements that describe what you want to achieve. They should inspire, engage, challenge, and motivate the team. Objectives are time-bound and qualitative.
On May 25, 1961, John F. Kennedy before the joint session of congress, set the following national goal:
 “I believe that this nation should commit itself to achieving the goal, before this decade is out, of landing a man on the moon and returning him safely to the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes a Good Objective?</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-makes-a-good-objective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:45:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/what-makes-a-good-objective/</guid>
      <description>Your objectives should be:
High impact Achieving a team objective should impact your organization. The achievement should be worthy of a celebration. Avoid creating “business as usual” objectives. We define “business as usual” objectives as those written based on what the team believes they can achieve without changing their behavior. Outcomes of this process are to help the team evolve, continue to innovate, and drive efficiency.
Clear Use clear language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Your Team Objective</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/discovering-your-team-objective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:39:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/discovering-your-team-objective/</guid>
      <description>The following questions are helpful in discovering your team objective:
 How can we contribute to one of the strategic objectives?
 Which of the key results associated with a strategic objective can we impact?
 Which area of our team’s performance would we want to improve the most to achieve a strategic objective?
 What area of excellence for our team could we improve to an even higher level to ensure the organization achieves a strategic objective?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Types of Objectives</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-three-types-of-objectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:29:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-three-types-of-objectives/</guid>
      <description>There are three types of objectives:
Strategic Objectives Strategic objectives are your organization’s high-level and longer-term objectives. Organizations typically set strategic objectives annually. The organization will review these objectives throughout the year. However, organizations may set strategic objectives more frequent with the understanding that overhead exists with managing these objectives. Organizations establish strategic objectives first before they set any other objective types.
Team Objectives Team objectives are tactical objectives created by a team.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>