<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on OK Commit</title>
    <link>http://www.okcommit.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on OK Commit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 12:51:49 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.okcommit.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Facilitation</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/services/facilitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 12:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/services/facilitation/</guid>
      <description>We can help your organization with your OKR process through a comprehensive OKR implementation tailored for your organization that includes strategy sessions, manager certification, remote coaching sessions, and launch reviews to ensure sustainable results.
The facilitation includes:
 An executive leadership 1-day strategy session to develop annual stategic objectives and key results for organziation. A manager 2-day training session to certify your managers in the OKC process and establish team objectives and key results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Coaching</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/services/remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/services/remote/</guid>
      <description>If you are not interested in a comprehensive OKR implementation, we can provide a series of remote coaching sessions for your internal coaches (shepherds) and webinars to help guide your managers in your OKR implementation.
Remote coaching is appropriate for teams with OKR process experience or other goal setting methodologies.
Interested in learning more? Fill out the form below and we will contact you with additional information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/services/officehours/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 12:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/services/officehours/</guid>
      <description>We provide one-off consultations to answer your OKR-related questions and help you diagnose adoption and process issues.
The hours can be used in various ways:
 Answer OKR process questions or specific questions about your OKR implementation. Diagnose &amp;ldquo;piping&amp;rdquo; issues with objectives and a lack of meaningful progress towards key results. Discuss adoption challenges with the OKR process. Answer specific questions about your implementation. Provide quick assessments of your OKR implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>