<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Commitments on OK Commit</title>
    <link>http://www.okcommit.com/tags/commitments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Commitments on OK Commit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 16:03:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.okcommit.com/tags/commitments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Commit to Ensure Your Success</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/commit-to-ensure-your-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 16:03:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/commit-to-ensure-your-success/</guid>
      <description>According to a recent study done by U.S. News, 80% of New Year’s resolution makers become New Year’s resolution breakers by the second week of February. Similarly, many organizations suffer a similar fate with their OKR implementation. A common mistake many teams make with their objectives and key results is that they “set and forget” goals.
In both cases, the reason they fail is that they don’t take small steps and review progress on a regular basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commitment Meeting Best Practices</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/commitment-meeting-best-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:19:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/commitment-meeting-best-practices/</guid>
      <description>This article discusses some logistics and best practices for your commitment meetings.
Types of Meetings Depending on your commitment type, you have a few options for your meetings:
 Commitment meetings are 10-15 minutes long and cover the 4-question agenda. Most teams will use commitment meetings. Commitment meetings are best when the team makes small outcome commitments or uses projects to influence the key results. Commitment huddles are 5 minutes long and are best when using leveraged behavior commitments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Types of Commitments</title>
      <link>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-three-types-of-commitments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.okcommit.com/learn/the-three-types-of-commitments/</guid>
      <description>Making regular commitments towards the key results is where the real execution takes place. Let’s discuss how to tailor commitment making for your team.
Types of Commitments There are three types of commitments to consider:
 Leveraged behaviors track the specific behaviors you want the team to perform throughout the week. It holds the team accountable for performing the behavior rather than producing the result. You can track leveraged behaviors on an individual or team basis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>